https://www.ukhost4u.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHostingWeb HostingWordPress HostingReseller HostingEnterprise HostingDomains & SSLDomain RegistrationSSL CertificatesTransfer A DomainServersVPS HostingDedicated ServersWebsite BuilderWebsite Builder PackageProfessional Web DesignVOIPDatabase Solutions3CX VOIP SolutionsContact & SupportClient AreaKnowledge BaseBlogSubmit Support TicketCall Us: 0330 088 5790HostingWeb HostingChoose from our affordable, flexible, powerful shared hosting plansEnterprise HostingEnjoy the best speeds and resources possible with Enterprise SSD HostingWordPress HostingHost your Wordpress website quickly and affordablyReseller HostingMake money from web hosting with our reseller hosting packagesDomains & SSLDomain RegistrationAcquire your online identity, choosing from over 900 domain extensionsSSL CertificatesProtect your website with an SSL certificate and show your a trusted sourceTransfer DomainTransfer your domain name to us in just minutesServersVirtual Machine HostingSuperfast, scalable Virtual Machines at affordable pricesDedicated ServersTake control with our high performance, reliable Dedicated ServersHosted DesktopWindows 10 hosted desktop environment (DaaS)Website BuilderWebsite BuilderCreate a stunning website in minutes, with no knowledge requiredProfessional Web DesignNeed a little more assistance getting online? Our designers can help.VOIP3CX VOIP PBX SolutionsBuild the ideal PBX for your SME business which can grow with youFreePBX Hosted PBXFreePBX is a web-based open source PBX based on AsteriskGeneral Privacy StatementUKHost4u respects the privacy of the personal information given to us. Personal or business details such as your name, street address and e-mail address, or any other business or personal information you may provide will not be given out to any third parties persons or companies unless we are explicitly required to do so in order to provide services requested, such as domain name registration.UKHost4u contains links to third-party websites for which we have no control over their content, nor the way other sites regulate their readers personal information. UKhost4u cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies or content of other web sites. However UKHost4u has taken time and care to make sure the links provided are to genuine sites of a responsible nature. We urge you where possible to read their privacy policy and assure yourself that your information is safe before giving out your personal details.Privacy Policy for UKHost4uWe, Host4u Limited, have designed this privacy policy to set out how we handle personal information. It covers Host4u Limited (Company Number: C75324) and its wholly owned subsidiaries UKHost4u, Host4u, AUHost4u and the web sites associated with our brand.When we refer to ‘we’, ‘us’ or ‘Host4u’, we are referring to Host4u Limited and all related subsidiaries. If we refer to ‘policy’ we’re referring to this privacy policy. If we refer to ‘user terms’ we’re referring to the rules for using each of the Sites. Take the time to read this in full. By using any of our Sites, you agree to this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our web sites or any affiliated services.Information we collect.We collect certain personal information about visitors and users of our Sites. The most common types of information we collect are user names, names, email addresses, other contact details, payment information such as payment details, transactional details, support queries, forum comments and analytics data.How we collect personal information. We may collect personal information directly when you provide it to us, when you have given us your consent for this information to be collected.When you provide personal information to us you are consenting to us collecting and using that information in line with this policy and the terms of our service. You are likely to provide personal information when you complete membership registration.If you choose not to provide personal information, we may not be able to provide you with any service.Personal information we collect about you from others. We generally collect personal information directly from you, we may on occasion also collect information about you from other sources (such as a payment gateway) and by using tracking technologies such as cookies.How do we use personal information. We may use your personal information in order for us to provide you with services, update you with news and information, provide you with information that you request, carry out technical analysis, monitor activity, resolve support requests, or manage our relationship with you.When may we disclose your personal information? We may disclose personal information to parties like subcontractors and service providers, professional advisers, regulators and government authorities.We use a network of subcontractors and service providers in order to ensure that we maintain the best possible service. Some of the subcontractors and service providers to whom we may disclose your personal information, like service providers who provide us with technical support, are based outside Europe. In order to protect your information, we take care where possible to work with subcontractors and service providers who we believe maintain an acceptable standard of data security compliance.How do we store your personal information. We store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us. Personal information that we store is subject to security and access controls, including username and password authentication and data encryption where appropriate.How can you access your personal information. You can access some of the information that we collect about you by logging in to yourclient You also have the right to make a request to access any other information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that information.Control of your personal information. Where we have your consent to do so, we may send you marketing communications about products and services. You can ‘opt-out’ of such communications if you would prefer using the unsubscribe option.Information about children.Our products are not suitable for children under the age of 18 years, so if you are under 18 we ask that you do not use our products or give us your personal information.Information you make public. If you make your personal information available to other people, we cannot control or accept responsibility for the way they will use or manage that information.Update to this policy. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to make sure it stays up to datein line with our policies. When we do amend the policy, the changes will be effective immediately.How can you contact us? If you have any questions about our privacy practices or have any concerns about how we have been managing your personal information please Contact Us and ask for your email to be passed to the management team.
